okay here we go so a little bit of a
smile and try to keep it during the
meditation just it's a Mona Lisa smile
nice on recess until the Mona Lisa cows
mantenere durante telemedicine and the
eyelids are relaxed those purple Arella
hollows try to relax like don't get too
serious about your yoga and don't get
too serious about your meditation
indenter a la carte a not pongas nemecio
silicone a yoga Nicola meters you try
not to be tense
try not to try too hard intent on or
start dancin I it's a beautiful day
sandy away you we have a beautiful lake
Chalobah outside then was a little more
solo go to Cherlapally afuera we are
sitting with beautiful friends estamos
in Pelican Bay yasser moses amigos we
had a good yoga and I had a good
cappuccino do we must know when a
practical yoga a two-in-one cappuccino
everything's relaxed louis post a VA mr.
La Jolla
we like your fingers jalaja los dedos
pull in your stomach slightly that will
straighten your lower spine mentally
ferment a toast Omega para steer our
genders are the spinner or Serena
portulaca with larger forehead like a
baby's forehead relative friend the como
la Frontera movie
and slowly come to prayer momentum Entei
attention gospel CEO and start to follow
your breath in tempest a yearlong
respiration gently and happily focus on
your breath and try not to think about
too many other things so a momentum folk
attempt or SP ratio condor surah intent
on dono pensar en otras cosas
long exhales solution is Larkins
then we'll go to a desire around state
of mind
they sell rain or the sale you can focus
your mind on for example on some outer
noise in the room passing for God to
maintain el Ganso needle in this room
today we have a pretty loud
air-conditioner autonomous phone I
recognition alone
we have bird noises outside Park
currents we have some hotel staff doing
things outside making some noise in
personam the rotor Lucinda sonidos
sometimes a person inside the room
coughs or make some noise so near the
end enteral itis urine so pick one of
those for me the air conditioner is
strongest in his coach even opera me
later conditioners in Maserati and
focused on this desire around state of
mind in forgotten s testamental the rain
or the sale
every step up through the form and
formless realm levels que paso del
recorrido already know the forming of
formal is an exercise in comparison as
nature CCO the comparison we focus on
the love of that were at right now lots
of them focus on annual the order for
example the air conditioner in the
desirable later conditional neuronal the
self or impure and then we compare it to
the next level deeper into the object
below local Paris LC Antony well perfume
visas and an object and next object
we're gonna choose is the first level of
the former yep siento que tu es el
primer annual the ramela formal it's
actually the state of mind which creates
a formula birth if you die in that state
of mind or having practiced that state
of mind about stellastot mental sim
Juarez and nasty moment in this a
memento drink Arneson Renault la forma
hace la practica hace mucho tiempo soul
at the customs anywhere and we're gonna
make the comparison by using our
heartbeat
ill a comparison los acero till Sandow
to lateral Corazon so please move your
attention from the air-conditioner maybe
attenzione there's a lighter conditional
row to the heartbeat inside your chest
Estela tol to Corazon and to pecho
dentro to page and naturally you'll have
a feeling that it's much quieter to
follow the heartbeat then to follow the
air-conditioner natural mentation tendrá
el sentimiento the case dama Silencio so
Bohnert attention and Lotito Candelaria
condition
the rough awareness of your mind
noticing things la conciencia generally
saw two men take acquainted causes which
in Sanskrit is called vitarka the mother
with turkan sanskrit oh that's focusing
now on the air conditioner or stop
Westall attention and a lighter
conditioner and then the part of your
mind that wants to go deeper para la
parte de tu mente ketoprofen me sir
which are which are we all go to the
hearty sav-a-lot ido
it's like hearing a song on the on the
loudspeaker at the grocery store moscow
charge
una cancion and el Supermercado that
vitarka
vitarka and then if you pass and stand
without moving in the grocery store to
listen to some detail of the song see
the TNS I'm aware taper escuchar la
cancion Alitalia Yunus but specifically
that's the channel that's more like
digging into the object going deeper
into the object examining the object as
which era eskimo Profundis are
penetrating allah prophetic seminary
loop yet so classically in this movement
from the desire realm to the former la
presentación is classic as a momento de
el reno el deseo axillary NOLA formal
your rough awareness rough noticing is
looking at the air conditioner too
conscientious general Starr and focal
analyzer conditional and then your
examination looking deeper e2 capacitor
examiner oh this criminal stir profundus
and amass that's looking into the
formula then trail run on a former and
seeing the quiet beating of your heart
in your chest
Percy viendo el silencio solitude
Corazon
than pipette you so slowly now seek a
lentil minting let's focus on the
air-conditioner and then look ahead into
the formula at the heart and move into
the heart into observing the heartbeat I
seek a movie potency on the lighter
conditional a la tierra del Corazon get
observe and you are outside the heart
you are watching heart heartbeat estas a
fuera del lot al Corazon observe and
alone
the transition will take a few minutes
the transition the URL knows minutos
each step up in this meditation paso
kevin season ul and estimate Monsieur
requires an a gotcha of meditation the
Kirika tectus elaborate on agarró la
gotcha
you will leave something behind because
it's not as quiet as the place you want
to go abandon Aras algo por que no es
tan Silencio so como el lugar al cual
Kara's it here and the process of
leaving behind what is not so quiet to
go to a more quiet place will take a few
minutes el proceso de abandoner lo que
no está en Silencio so e dear he
returned lugar my Silencio so tomorrow
who knows minuto so let's make that
transition to a more quiet place the
beating of your heart Sakura eres es a
transition on lugar más Silencio
solitaire tu corazon
notice that the concentration on your
heartbeat has a nice effect on your body
the prana is moving nice and you feel
some kind of nice alignment in your
meditation in your posture Toma
conciencia de que toe tension play
Mennella tol Corazon esta Kane Rondo una
Linea she own you know ami Antonietta Co
por todo cuerpo de pro se mucho placer
there's a feeling almost of pleasant
relief that you are in a more quiet
place called heartbeat you're watching
the heartbeat and it's more quiet and
pleasant La Senza Sione's en olivio
place entero
for Iran lugar massive ensues
now I move from the first forum realm
love of meditation to the second muscle
premiere me where the former el segundo
the two mental functions of vitarka and
vichara noticing the heart beating and
focusing more deeply on heart beating as
a observer we talk of Achara
the last cuenta the lateral to corazón y
tambien roughen veces en el as we enter
the second form a leland trundle and el
segundo knee where those two qualities
of the mind will drop out completely
Aven Donna's completamente s as those
characteristic as a lament and there'll
be a sensation of not watching her data
but staying in the heart embedding a
tendril a sense a see own take a
Avendano cell observable or deleterious
own y el placer deparment serenella t el
corazon esther dentro de la TiVo try to
make the second transition intenta
general esta segunda transition dropped
rougher state of mind noticing jackie
Aven dona los Estados mental desmos
danzo's the attention general isa exam
the discrimination examination delegate
and drill down deeper into objects
become the tearing of the heart he
Panetta NL objeto
convert en tonality el corazon
there's still a awareness of the
alignment the present alignment of the
body
sigue extendo la conciencia tell play
santero sentimiento de la la nación de
tu cuerpo especially if you've been
doing your yoga practice every day a
special mentis es esta practical no yoga
the area and there is this pleasant
sensation because it's more quiet to be
the heartbeat dennah days to watch the
jardin La Senza see own s placenta
report a s mess police antara ser el a t
el corazon observe our low
now we move to the third forum not a
bomb shelter sir newald
nella former the big difference here
lagron diferencia key is that the
pleasant feeling of the mind the
pleasant feeling of the choir if girls
la sensation Pleasant era delicate to
evil Silencio mental that becomes a
obstacle in this test moment to use a
computer in an obstacle and honor and
you drill down deeper into the object in
the net respond Ament and elaborate now
you're not thinking about oh it's so
nice it's so quiet
European says yes the more latency let's
use you just be quiet without thinking
always so nice Celeste us kiya seemed
when Sir Kay when the sister feel a
deeper kind of quiet naked tooth must
perform at this level to meditation
tools of the mind are well developed
strong the key in destiny well Azaz
aramean test merit at the asylum
intestine we end the cell reales your
smoke alarm session your smoke alarm is
very sensitive now to a lot of money
almost moisten Ceylon este momento
shishun if the mind tries to go back to
the air conditioner si la mantequilla
Salida conditional or even if it tries
to watch the heartbeat
instead of being hurt being or seeing
then
observer-relative el corazon embezzler
Corazon or even if it says to yourself
this is nice this is so quiet for
inclusive cetera say as testimony y nos
system we didn't see oh so then that
smoke alarm will make a small peepee
peep in your mind as a larva the whare
active our own alarm and to maintain my
mind has gone back to the air
conditioner
Oh lament moment is valera conditional
then there's another meditation tool in
your mind
yeah otra aramean Tomita event
despondent to maintain it's like a cook
in a rope
es como una cuerda yunnan swallow and it
hooks the mind that's looking at the air
conditioner in ganja a lament Acosta
observe and allow the conditioner and it
pulls it back into the super quiet
heartbeat being the hardened lava well
way al super Silencio so estado de ser
la de el corazon so now we are the hardy
to warez in Latur chorus on our and
we've gone deeper in the third former
realm novel justice Maspero phone alert
ooh sir newald adrenal of former deeper
then thinking oh this is really nice and
quiet
mucho mas profundo cal pensamiento
depends the center or estrus delicioso
meant a Silencio so we went to an even
more quiet place just us and then
regarding Clouseau mas Silencio
now let's move to the fourth forum novel
oral Bertoni where the LA forum
the pleasant alignment of the body
Lalli Niazi own delicious el cuerpo
especially if you've been doing yoga
especially anything see practicas yoga
regular mental drops out Vandana esta
sensation placental well it's a
distraction in the fourth form Nava is
nice traction and apart only well the
Rinella foramen to be aware of how good
it feels to have a good alignment during
in your posture humanitarian posture a
star consciente como se siente tener una
when Alan ASEAN and the poster animators
you cancel that one donation
each time we move up we cancel something
okay advances I want Donna's alumina so
Kinsella salvo in the fourth forum level
an important evil del rey de la forma
focus on deep quiet forgot a an El
Silencio por phone go beyond pleasant
mental feeling and a pleasant physical
feeling masala sensation Pleasant Tara
physical mental and make a special
effort yes one is for so special to feel
as though you're focused on a single
point Center como si Asturias info kado
a noon so Lepanto find a single point of
an a feeling or a sensation of single
point ms o encontrar el sentimiento de
la concentration on upon 12 beyond
physical or emotional feelings esta
Messiah Alison
mentis pleasant arrows Mentalist
officials will stay here for a few
minutes after mascara most knows me
notice still inside the beating heart
tears enternity el corazon
now we'll move to the first formless
realm level what a vassal premier nivel
del rey knows informal which is called
naam kya or in the space long kurta
Espace infinite simply take that single
point rasa concentration it won't turn
stay on a single point
ans a concentration upon 12 drop the
beating heart
leave the beating heart behind either a
Vandana ality el corazon surreality el
corazon only the single point now for a
solar concentration upon turn way beyond
noticing and checking mo import and
super and o Turkish examiner etirsa
cuenta get the means even don't know and
way beyond the feeling the pleasant
feeling of your posture and pleasant
feeling of the quiet the super and the
messiah the Vela sensation placenta a
physical mental the body knows as though
it was anesthetized
cuerpo conscious tyrannous this year
we're in one single point moving into
the formless realm concentration upon 12
a sinhala transition and Raynaud's
informal now think about space that
holds our planet our Sun our stars en el
espacio sorrel colistin los planet a
cell solar sister alia and begin to
stretch out from that single point
there's a say Punto extended
extend the focus to
all of space start like a wave coming
from a single point extend a to
concentration a total spaz you come on
now and expand Shiva it's easier for me
if I stay in the horizontal plane but a
miasmas fossils imitator in the plan
horizontally and it's easier for me if I
just think of going left and right he is
mass fácil para pensar the gmail is Kara
what a wretch as you get more experience
in the meditation come for my violence
and not experience here you can increase
that to front and back well as it as in
frontier sutras and up and down the
river
yahwah so imagine your mind imagine not
to maintain flowing away from you in
either direction from that single point
flow yendo expand beyond oh saying
culturally direction so he knows the
serpent continually expanding for the
next few minutes expansion continued Rho
C NTS B notice in all of space tourists
pass in tourist bus no awareness of the
your physical environment or body
anymore gen-i conciencia the tumour
ambient and yet the choir
now I move to the second formless realm
for a long serve Segundo Knievel's
informal we always leave something
behind to drill down deeper
alakay broken dishes deep Anitra's
energy Antony well Avendano salvo in the
first formless realm Lama in
pre-medieval sin formal we were
imagining the mind moving from a single
point to all of endless space machinist
lamenting haciendo and as expansive
essential espacio finito so like a boat
on an ocean come on bark on uno say no
we were using the ocean as to chart our
position estimate estábamos usando loc
ah no para localizer Westra position but
that's also a distraction pero su CNO
was passing finito instruction so in the
second formless realm the second MC in
El Segundo numerals informal we dropped
this imagination of endless space le -
Yvonne Donna's Lima he nación de
l'espace infinitive
we dropped places where we can measure
where we are
Aven donas lo lagares monopod areas
tomar movida Eve estancia the -
localization and we move into pure
consciousness pure awareness even atrás
en la atención buena de la hora
conciencia no more points of reference
leaving the
who knows the reference we are
meditating inside of an endless
awareness estas merit and oh then trona
infinite de conciencia
even thinking about endless awareness
inclusive answer in the conscience
infinita take some kind of africa
'shakira chaos algún the police were so
it reduces our concentration la cual
Desiree discussed oh concentration let's
move to the third formless realm
meditation all of us el tercer nev and
andreas informal
what will we drop gavin dullness drop
this perception of infinite awareness i
want on the perception de la contains
infinite and move into the third
formless realm
sinhala transition after cern even seem
formal where you are no longer holding
anything
it's just nothing than the youngest us
in fecundity or sustain en de ninguna
Peto no holder
no I Navy a Christian II no holding me
in accion the sustaining nothing to hold
onto
Nina case Austin a drop the infinite
awareness
I wondered rockin since infinity
now we move to the fourth formless realm
double by myself cuarto seem for money
well it takes some effort to think I'm
not holding on to anything and no one's
holding Sara quieres for so pensar yo
estoy sustain yendo nada no info Canova
ninguna keto me tampoco i a lien case
I'm on a patent elección them
let's go to a deeper the deepest
kind of quiet almost like etude mass
profunda the effort to hold on to
nothing unless were so para learn
forgotten it feels like some kind of
darkness so cinta c'mon a special
courier and all the levels before that
felt like some kind of distracting
effort he lost new LS previous accenting
communist for so Destructo so in the
fourth formless realm lava the second
quarto near L sin for a man I choose not
to choose let's go home North go here I
will not think about any particular
object like infinite awareness no pencil
anyone objeto particular como conscience
infinita
and I also choose not to think about
holding on to nothing también es koko de
sido no pens are in area and open
certain info Carmen are beyond our
choice Messiah atoll elección
I choose a deeper kind of nothing s
cocoa una nada mas por funda
now that my mind is in a nice space or a
tournament system when Espace here I
will start the real meditation pasaría
said la verdadera Metis Yan I will place
in front of my mind on referent a
momentum holy arching will not help us a
girl a teacher la maestra master and the
emptiness of that teacher is soo Aquila
those nine state of mind before this was
no any wellness they mated those
previous starting with the air
conditioner can pass an analyzer
conditioner going to the for formal
novels pasando por las cuatro novellas
delle Foreman go into the for formless
realm novels pasando por las cuatro new
lesson for man those were exercises in
sharpening my ability to meditate trance
Oliver CC espera
Fortaleza me capacidad method Viva
they feel good she's in tambien it feels
like real meditation for a second okay
resist does merit and all aware that I
found spaces in my meditation that I
never reached before you got a lugar SME
meditation
a La Scala's nunca access alone but I
understand those are only instruments
they are not gone pero entiendo que son
soul instrumentos no son lameta
it's like building a powerful microscope
eskimo concentrate on Luke Rosco purple
arrows the point is not a microscope
look at even a cell microscope you know
the point is what I put under the
microscope after I build a rocket EOS
lepetit upon a microscope is Posey
construal microscope
so I I realized those eight states of
mind are very attractive my cuenta que
so such as tells me that they were sunmo
attract evils
they're almost addicting like the donut
so Nike was come on churro and children
but I I know to to help myself and
others Rajasekhar para ayudar me yeah
you wrote rose I need to focus the
microscope and and something holy mesito
and for Carl microscopy on analogous a
girl so I choose my heart teacher as
coho
mallamma Corazon any teacher in your
life who has helped you not call care
maestro maestro catelleya moochin to
either your mother and father are very
powerful and holy teachers for each one
of us - father - Mallorie
son Seguros monstrous and then all your
school teachers all the teachers who
taught you your occupation ptosis
masters el escorial was kept dancing
Aaron - profession and spiritual
teachers or priests or maestro spirit
Alice mosa serratus choose one s : and
bring them to meditate with you in front
of your mind in Vita law see trial as a
mater contigo frente to mental choose
one is coffee oh no make them real this
is not meditating on a photograph or a
painting or a statue we are focusing on
a real person and oh as l'oreal estamos
meetin an imaginary stato estamos mate
and Oh
and we'll sell BB&T their chest is
moving with the breath same wave a super
tucano respira see on their eyes are
blinking so Soho's rebellion their face
has a smile so color the illness Andres
there's the fragrance server of a good
person coming from their body
you know Ned oh man don't serve wine Oh
a man and I support even this teacher
inclusive as emptiness yesterday maestro
maestro tennis walk we don't what is the
emptiness of this teacher so let's walk
alone there's no teacher in my life who
came into my life without a climax in my
master Oh Oh master anivia
yeah oh yeah you got me we don't see no
eres umbrella no Sammy Academy Caprivi
right now the teacher sitting in front
of me
the next moment all maestro centaur
entity is coming out of a karmic seed in
my own mind so here in a semi a chemical
problem entity beautiful silver karmic
seeds in my own mind the easy mass email
samia's blood tiara sentimental our
opening never ends small images of this
nama are coming out
bikini I see Martinez Nestor Lama
stencil in one after another on the
resort and they present themselves to my
mind suppressant and Anthony went and
that's what it is to meditate on my
number yet so significant a telling me
lament so for just one minute
CK one minute try to imagine those a
silver seed in the back of your mind
intent imaginary semia la tra la petit
Rosetta meant a try to imagine the seed
opening in Makena cono sur la semilla
and try to imagine the llama coming up
imagine a day a llama
sir handel desde muffin it's a picture
but it's a perfect picture assume
imagine Paris perfecta it's a real
number
remember the era lemon and it can teach
me to become a Buddha to make planes in
air combat Airmen emboldened try to
imagine the silver seed and try to
imagine the Lama coming out intent
imagine art a Samia Plataea a Lama su
tienda de yeah
as long as I have these seats I will
have another interesting mr. Samia
standard a llama as long as I have these
seats I will have a mama interesting as
the Samia standard a llama
who put the seed in my mind came postal
as a million in mentem I did your Luiza
mainly when was it principalmente quando
in my past life
Maria Posada do you remember planting
this in the chorus Arles umbrella
probably not Laura mminton is the memory
somewhere in your mind a castle of a
forest and Willow guarded to maintain
yes
seeing so let's pretend we remember but
a finger recorder
think about your nama being sent to Lama
think about the laws of karma being
centralized el carmen law number one
primarily all the forces that created
the kind of Lama
I have must have been the same kind of
thing that I did in the past todas las
fuerzas owner just que creer on LP
Palama cutting Laura and ever sido el
mismo tipo Energia en pasado las casas
que pase a here our second law of karma
second delay del Carmen I've known my
nama four oh four years five years ten
years
Camila manager Sara cuatro Sinko the
assignments but karma cause there are
lots immediate army come maybe it was
only a few days it so let it be anyone
knows the yes maybe it was a very
special hour spent with them in my past
life
kisses la sombra durante nausea so
kisses durante una hora
moysha linaria pasado
maybe they were a completely different
person like maybe a male was a female
maybe
American was a Saudi Arabian kiss-ass
Aruna persona completamente Stinton
embracing una mujer y visa versa
Estonian siendo they are away Selita
maybe I was a different person
mrs. joy and a person s Tintin maybe I
was male or female Jesus Iran represents
Arabic where I lived in another country
maybe another police maybe the seed was
planted thousands of years ago he said
was a mere force umbrella semi lays
their news so now even if we cannot
remember planting the seed for a nama
Yossi no puede recorder or several SME
apollomon let's pretend we remember
thinking at the chorus let's imagine ma
him let your imagination go go very very
free libera completamente to imaginación
creator movie genera una película
excitement adventure emotion ventura
romance romance make a beautiful story
of your past life a scenario system
Astoria Twitter Purcell whatever comes
into your mind looking at the moon
because whatever comes in to your mind
is coming from the same seed that
created your namah porque lo que viene
de menthe winner las mismas me a sticker
onto llama and if you keep doing this
meditation you see capacity you see
continuous en estimate SEO you will be
able to look backwards in the wheel of
life whereas persevere as yet receiver a
la vida and you will see the actual
events that have planted your life now
mercy with us
no Sorrento's relays kisum learn to
adapt well okay five minutes on your
personal movie Cinco minutos and to
película personal every day for our 30
day meditation challenge the other one
to drink them in el desafío de train
terminal toes you can make it more
grande real possessor mas Grande osa you
can add more detail yoga guru Mathai
five minutes Cinco minutos on the
meeting between you and your nominal
encuentro entropy dilemma in your past
life the apostle that planted that
silver seed in your mind case umbrella
semi applicant to mint
then please come back to the present
moment in your meditation
Butwell moment the presenting to me to
see if my mama is coming from those
seeds similar may be necessary years
then my Nami has emptiness malama honua
Cuidad because emptiness means or color
Aquila significant there's no Lama in my
life can ye Lama and me maintain which I
did not create in no idea yo creo previa
Monty now come back to your breath will
be a large piracy on three long breaths
trace acceleration is Larry with each
exhale come collect Selassie on a golden
Knight coming from you
una Luz Dorada came solidity and
spreading to the people of this world
que salen Vyasa tolas personas este
mundo sharing your good karma of this
meditation and compartir not to incur
mathematician with each living being
don't go serve evil
then you can slowly open your eyes he
displays gentlemen - please hurry - so
take a stretch that's called the dance
of the lion Isis am Aladdin sir Leon was
taught by the future Buddha Maitreya
when Singapore el Toro 23 - a Sangha and
mastress Sangha 1700 years ago a same in
cetacean - sang nose and body starts as
you said it was very sad but lo t listen
after they see emptiness directly
dispersed they persevere directa mental
of acquittal in the in the minutes after
death the antennas directly in las me
notice posterior SS pasilla perception
the rectal area to understand more about
emptiness and the wheel of life para
desarrollar una mejor compression de la
bahia de la la vida